<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!-- TAGS SHOULD BE SEPARATED BY SPACES-->

<!-- LINKS IN THE BODY TEXT SHOULD BE FORMATTED AS
    &lt;a href="ADDRESS">NAME&lt;/a> -->
<!-- LINE BREAKS SHOULD BE FORMATTED AS
    &lt;br> -->

<resources>
    <string-array name="chairmans_about">
        <item>fragment_pager_item_no_image</item>
        <item>What is Chairman\'s?</item>
        <item>As stated in the FRC Manual section 6.4.1: \"The Chairman\'s Award was created to keep
            the central focus of FRC on the ultimate goal of transforming the culture in ways that
            will inspire greater levels of respect and honor for science and technology, as well as
            encouraging more of today\'s youth to become scientists, engineers, and technologists.
            &lt;br>The Chairman\'s Award represents the spirit of FIRST. It honors the team that, in
            the judges\' estimation, best represents a model for other teams to emulate, and which
            embodies the goals and purpose of FIRST. It remains FIRST\'s most prestigious award.\"
            &lt;br>Any non-rookie team can compete for the Chairman\'s Award. It focuses on a team\'s
            current and previous year. The Chairman\'s Award is one of three ways to qualify for the
            FIRST Championship. The winners are given the opportunity to compete at the FIRST
            Championship to be inducted into the First Hall of Fame. The FIRST Hall of Fame consists
            of teams that have won the Chairman’s Award at the FIRST Championship. A new rule for the
            2014 season states that a team can compete for the Chairman\'s Award at every regional they
            attend until they win. In previous seasons, teams could only compete at one regional event.
            &lt;br>Chairman\'s is composed largely of three different pieces: the written portion,
            the speech, and the video.</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="chairmans_writing">
        <item>fragment_pager_item_no_image</item>
        <item>The Written Portion</item>
        <item>The written piece of Chairman’s has two main parts, the essay and the executive
            summary. The essay is a 10,000 character written explanation of how your team spreads
            the mission of FIRST. At first 10,000 characters can seem like a lot, but you will most
            likely have to shrink your essay in order to meet these requirements. While writing your
            essay do not worry about word count. You will be better off writing your essay and them
            combining and removing sentences. It\'s important that you start your essay early that way
            your speech and video can play off of it.
            &lt;br>The executive summary is a series of questions that you will have to answer. The
            majority of the questions have a 500 character word limit. You will also include your
            team name, number and sponsors. These short answers have to do with how your team has
            spread FIRST, and how FIRST has impacted your team. Along with the written pieces, you
            will need to submit four photos at the same time. These photos are to show judges how
            you’ve spread FIRST. These four photos can be no more than 1.0 MB of memory.</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="chairmans_speech">
        <item>fragment_pager_item_no_image</item>
        <item>The Speech</item>
        <item>Although teams can probably talk about how they spread the mission of FIRST for hours,
            teams are only given a short five minute time period to tell judges all about how they
            impact their community. After the five minute presentation time, teams will have a five
            minute question answer session. Teams must send in up to three representatives - members
            or mentors.
            &lt;br>&lt;br>The Chairman\'s presentation can seem very scary but here are some tips to
            keep in mind while creating and performing your presentation:
            &lt;br>&lt;br>&#8226;\tDon\'t let the judges emotions get to you. They have had long days of
            speeches and are probably very tired and bored. Don\'t let this get to you while presenting.
            &lt;br>&lt;br>&#8226;\tThe room may be very small; you should bring only what is necessary.
            &lt;br>&lt;br>&#8226;\tExactly how much time you have depends on the judges. Some judges may start
            the clock when you open the door.</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="chairmans_video">
        <item>fragment_pager_item_no_image</item>
        <item>The Video</item>
        <item>The Chairman\'s video can be no longer than three minutes nor shorter than one. The
            Chairman\'s video is mandatory in order to compete for the award. Before judges make
            their final decision as to who wins between a few final teams, they watch these videos.
            The video is very important because it is the last thing the judges will remember. When
            a team wins, the video is broadcasted to the rest of the teams on the big screen at regional
            or district events.</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
</resources>