<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!-- TAGS SHOULD BE SEPARATED BY SPACES-->

<!-- LINKS IN THE BODY TEXT SHOULD BE FORMATTED AS
    &lt;a href="ADDRESS">NAME&lt;/a> -->
<!-- LINE BREAKS SHOULD BE FORMATTED AS
    &lt;br> -->

<resources>
    <string-array name="spirit_importance">
        <item>fragment_pager_item_no_image</item>
        <item>Importance of Spirit</item>
        <item>While at competitions it\'s important that you make your team known. The more noticed you
            are by other teams, the more likely you are to get picked for alliance selections. You
            also want to keep the competition energy high because it makes an even more exciting
            atmosphere for everyone in the arena.</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="spirit_team_image">
        <item>fragment_pager_item_no_image</item>
        <item>Team Image</item>
        <item>Before competition it is important to develop a team image or look. This look can be
            fun and exciting; teams wear everything from animal costumes to capes and crowns, each
            team coming up with their own look. It can be difficult to make your own image, but just
            keep in mind that it doesn\'t have to be crazy to be recognizable. As winners of the FIRST
            World Championship Imagery Award, KING TeC shows that you don’t have to look over the top
            for your team to stand out.
            &lt;br>
            Start with a team t-shirt. Make your team name and number easily read, this way if another
            team or a judge is looking for your team, you’re easy to find. After developing a shirt, the
            sky is the limit. Teams wear everything from matching shoes, to matching bracelets. Be creative
            and remember to not shy far from your name. If teams will wonder how your mascot is relevant to
            your name, it’s probably not the best idea.</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="spirit_swag">
        <item>fragment_pager_item_no_image</item>
        <item>Swag</item>
        <item>Swag is a giveaway item for other teams. Although swag is far from mandatory, it can
            help advertise your team. Many teams do buttons, while at competition you can see people
            completely covered in buttons. Other simple and cost effective ideas are pencils and
            bracelets. Swag gets your team name and number out to other teams. Continue to keep in
            mind your message, your image, and how you want other teams to remember you.</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
</resources>