<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!-- LAYOUT OF CONTENT
    <string-array name="RESOURCE-ID">
        <item>LAYOUT NAME</item>
        <item>TITLE</item>
        <item>MAIN TEXT</item>
        <item>IMAGE NAME</item>
        <item>TAGS</item>
    </string-array> -->

<!-- TAGS SHOULD BE SEPARATED BY SPACES-->

<!-- LINKS IN THE BODY TEXT SHOULD BE FORMATTED AS
    &lt;a href="ADDRESS">NAME&lt;/a> -->
<!-- LINE BREAKS SHOULD BE FORMATTED AS
    &lt;br> -->

<resources>
    <string-array name="module_building">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Building Modules</item>
        <item>Hopefully by now prototyping has shown you some viable strategies and mechanisms for
            the game. Prototypes are great for finding out what designs work well, but your robot should
            not be made of prototypes! It\'s time to start building modules out of the designs you have
            tested; even if not every component has been fully tested it is important to start
            building what you can as soon as you can!
            &lt;br>While building components in modular sections is often the most efficient workflow,
            where many people can work on assembly at once, it is important to remember that in the
            end every module must come together to form a robot. Don\'t forget to talk between
            work-groups to make sure that everybody is on the same page!</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="robot_assembly">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Putting it All Together</item>
        <item>When you are putting all of your components together, it is important to keep the robot
            as a whole in mind. Be sure that your mechanisms will not interfere with each other and
            that the mechanisms as well as the motors and electrical components that are required
            have enough room. Also think about the order in which you should attach the components.
            It\'s a good idea to start with your drive train or frame and then attach the other
            components onto it where they belong. Make sure you leave a little room for error on
            your frame, it\'s never fun when you have to make more room around your mechanisms so
            they can fit together properly. Keep your overall goal in mind and go one step at a time.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="beginning_wiring">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Starting Electrical</item>
        <item>Although it may seem absurd to start designing your electrical configuration without a
            complete robot, you\'re going to want to have the main board designed and built early so
            it can be installed on the chassis. Try to have all of your main electrical components in
            one place, so that parts can be swapped out if need be.
            &lt;br>Even though the electrical system is often designed to fit in a small, compact space
            it is important to not get carried away and create an impermeable board. Every electrical
            component on your robot will generate heat, and the last thing your team needs is part of
            the robot shutting down during competition from overheating. Consider ventilation when
            designing your system!
            &lt;br>Labelling parts of the system is also a critically important step; one which can
            never be started too early. If your team\'s main electrician is absent on competition day,
            would your team be able to fix any problems that arose?</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="thinking_about_programming">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Planning Programming</item>
        <item>Even though it may seem early to start planning your programming, during Week 3 of build
            season it is important to start narrowing down the specifics of your program. Think about
            how your code will be organized, and determine who will be responsible for programming each
            section of the robot.
            &lt;br>Talk with your electrical department and find out how the robot is going to be wired!
            Even if this information is tentative, it is helpful to know how your robot is configured,
            especially what ports each system is plugged into. This is also an excellent time to
            make sure your robot\'s firmware and computer\'s software is up to date. Not having the
            right updates can cause major problems at competition, and may even prevent you from passing
            inspection. Plan ahead so that your robot can compete!</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
</resources>