<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!-- LAYOUT OF CONTENT
    <string-array name="RESOURCE-ID">
        <item>LAYOUT NAME</item>
        <item>TITLE</item>
        <item>MAIN TEXT</item>
        <item>IMAGE NAME</item>
        <item>TAGS</item>
    </string-array> -->

<!-- TAGS SHOULD BE SEPARATED BY SPACES-->

<!-- LINKS IN THE BODY TEXT SHOULD BE FORMATTED AS
    &lt;a href="ADDRESS">NAME&lt;/a> -->
<!-- LINE BREAKS SHOULD BE FORMATTED AS
    &lt;br> -->

<resources>
    <string-array name="scouting_match">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Match Scouting</item>
        <item>One of the most essential roles in a team at competition is scouting. Observing other
            robots during matches will help your team make decisions about alliance partners, as
            well as provide inspiration for any future changes to your strategy. Your team should
            look for other robots that are compatible with your own – having three identical robots
            on the same team probably isn\'t the best strategy. Even if your team is not going to be
            an alliance captain it is important that you keep scouting; if your team is picked your
            alliance partners may turn to you for help picking the third robot and for strategy.
            Scouting in the stands is designed to give your team as much information as possible
            about the performance of other robots. Your team can record both qualitative and
            quantitative information, but should have a standardized system for recording information.
            &lt;br>On the field performance depends on more than just the robot, it also depends
            on the driver. Have your scouting crew look at how other teams perform under stress,
            and make note of any flaws in their strategy that your team can exploit.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="scouting_pits">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Match Scouting</item>
        <item>Pit scouting is a great way to see every robot up close. You are able to see specifics
            of the robot\'s design and also some features not necessarily apparent on the field. As a
            team you should record important details such as the weight, height, drive-train and
            scoring capabilities. While pit scouting can\'t give you information about on the field
            performance, it can give your team an idea of what robots to look out for and what robots
            to consider for specialty purposes, such as pushing opponents out of the way. Make sure
            to take pictures of each robot to help connect each team with their robot.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
</resources>