<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!-- LAYOUT OF CONTENT
    <string-array name="RESOURCE-ID">
        <item>LAYOUT NAME</item>
        <item>TITLE</item>
        <item>MAIN TEXT</item>
        <item>IMAGE NAME</item>
        <item>TAGS</item>
    </string-array> -->

<!-- TAGS SHOULD BE SEPARATED BY SPACES-->

<!-- LINKS IN THE BODY TEXT SHOULD BE FORMATTED AS
    &lt;a href="ADDRESS">NAME&lt;/a> -->
<!-- LINE BREAKS SHOULD BE FORMATTED AS
    &lt;br> -->

<resources>
    <string-array name="outreach_about">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Outreach</item>
        <item>Teams spread the mission of FIRST in many different ways. Outreach events are important
            to help get your team name out into the world of FIRST and out into your community. Your
            team can do many forms of outreach in order to spread the world of science and technology.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="outreach_mentoring">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Mentoring</item>
        <item>One way to spread STEM is through mentoring other teams. You might consider starting a
            FTC team to form a funnel program at your school into your FRC team. You can also start
            other teams in your surrounding area through presenting at their schools. Whether its FLL,
            FTC or FRC, kids are given the opportunity to learn about science and technology and FIRST
            is an exciting organization to have fun in.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="outreach_demonstrations">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Demonstrations</item>
        <item>Whether it is at your local grocery store or at a science museum, demonstrations are a
            great way to reach out to your local community. You can allow kids to drive the robots
            and teach adults about its benefits. Demonstrations are a great opportunity for your team
            to find interested people and get them involved. A few fun places to give demonstrations
            is at local schools, malls, and museums.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
</resources>