<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!-- LAYOUT OF CONTENT
    <string-array name="RESOURCE-ID">
        <item>LAYOUT NAME</item>
        <item>TITLE</item>
        <item>MAIN TEXT</item>
        <item>IMAGE NAME</item>
        <item>TAGS</item>
    </string-array> -->

<!-- TAGS SHOULD BE SEPARATED BY SPACES-->

<!-- LINKS IN THE BODY TEXT SHOULD BE FORMATTED AS
    &lt;a href="ADDRESS">NAME&lt;/a> -->
<!-- LINE BREAKS SHOULD BE FORMATTED AS
    &lt;br> -->

<resources>
    <string-array name="drive_practice">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Drive Practice</item>
        <item>When competing at competition, nothing can make or break your teams experience than how
            your drivers work together and with the robot. While six weeks is not a lot of time to build
            a robot, it is important to find time to let your drivers practice. The earlier the better,
            but the season goes fast and we often are only able to practice driving during the last few
            days of the build season.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="tweaking_programming">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Tweaking Programming</item>
        <item>While you hopefully have the main functionality of your robot programmed by this point,
            odds are you won\'t get everything perfect the first time. Your programmers should be focusing
            on fixing the major bugs and getting everything working, but after that it is time to bring
            in the drive team.
            &lt;br>
            Although programmers like to think they know everything about the robot,
            it is important to remind them that they most likely won\'t be driving it at competition.
            If they will be, your team has lucked out! If not, the programmers should sit down with the
            drive team and fine tune the controls until the drivers are content.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="late_build_changes">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Building the Unexpected</item>
        <item>Like the real world, build season is often full of unexpected surprises. In the case of
            a robot-building emergency, don\'t panic. Last minute changes happen on every team, and the
            important thing to remember is that you can continue building after the six weeks are over.
            &lt;br>
            You are allowed to bring a small amount of robot-related parts to competition, which means
            you can manufacture parts at home and install them on the first day of competition.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="bag_and_tag">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Bagging and Tagging</item>
        <item>While in the past your robot had to be crated up, in recent years a new procedure for sealing
            away your robot has been unveiled. All official events with the exception of the Championship are
            "Bag and Tag" events, meaning that your robot must be suffocated by a giant bag on the last day
            of Build Season. More information is available in the
            &lt;a href="http://frc-manual.usfirst.org/viewItem/8">administrative manual&lt;/a>.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
</resources>