<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!-- LAYOUT OF CONTENT
    <string-array name="RESOURCE-ID">
        <item>LAYOUT NAME</item>
        <item>TITLE</item>
        <item>MAIN TEXT</item>
        <item>IMAGE NAME</item>
        <item>TAGS</item>
    </string-array> -->

<!-- TAGS SHOULD BE SEPARATED BY SPACES-->

<!-- LINKS IN THE BODY TEXT SHOULD BE FORMATTED AS
    &lt;a href="ADDRESS">NAME&lt;/a> -->
<!-- LINE BREAKS SHOULD BE FORMATTED AS
    &lt;br> -->

<resources>
    <string-array name="preparing_for_next_year">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Preparing for Next Year</item>
        <item>After the competition season ends, everyone deserves a rest, but there is still a lot
            of work to do. Your team must decide what you will be doing with your robot. Maybe it
            performed so well in competition that you want to keep it in operating conditions for
            demonstrations, or teaching new members about your robot. Maybe you will want to take it
            all apart so you can reuse parts for next year’s robot. Either way, your workspace
            probably could use some cleanup and organization of tools and parts after the last six
            weeks of mayhem. As your team grows it is important to keep up on the organization of
            your workspace to facilitate safety and productivity, as well as avoid the expense of
            having to replace lost tools or robot parts.
            &lt;br>If your team seeks to compete for the chairman’s award next year, you have more
            work to do. Demonstrations in your community during the summer goes a long way towards
            a convincing judges of your teams’ positive impact. If you kept your robot in operating
            condition, all the better. It will be your greatest tool for attracting positive interest
            in your robotics team, and to promote FIRST. KING TeC showcases their robot in an annual
            town parade in August, and brings it to schools for demonstrations in the fall and spring.
            &lt;br>How will you attract the most talented kids for your team next year? September
            is the best month to begin promoting your team to potential new members. Even though
            the FRC game isn’t released until January, there is a steep learning curve to follow if
            your new members want to learn all there is to know about an FRC robot, how the
            competitions work, and building skills. KING TeC makes it a priority that all our members
            are familiar with operating the power tools and the proper safety procedures to follow.
            Senior members can host classes in CAD or programming for the new members to learn essential
            software skills that will reap benefits during the competition season.
            &lt;br>To prepare new students for the intense atmosphere of first robotics competitions,
            consider using last years’ robot to compete at a mock regional in the fall. Older teams
            host small scale unofficial competitions in their high schools in the fall in order to
            train new members for the roles they will have at an actual competition. In Minnesota,
            KING TeC hosts the Minne-mini regional at their high school, where around 30 teams compete
            for a day. Search the Chief Delphi forums for practice competitions in your area.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
</resources>