<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- LAYOUT OF CONTENT
     <string-array name="RESOURCE-ID">
        <item>LAYOUT NAME</item>
        <item>TITLE</item>
        <item>MAIN TEXT</item>
        <item>IMAGE NAME</item>
        <item>TAGS</item>
    </string-array> -->
    <!-- TAGS SHOULD BE SEPARATED BY SPACES-->

    <!-- LINKS IN THE BODY TEXT SHOULD BE FORMATTED AS
        &lt;a href="ADDRESS">NAME&lt;/a> -->
    <!-- LINE BREAKS SHOULD BE FORMATTED AS
        &lt;br> -->

    <!-- Week One -->

    <string-array name="brainstorming">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Brainstorming</item>
        <item>Leaving Kickoff, the first thing your team should begin doing is
            brainstorming. No idea is a bad idea here, and this is the time to come up with all kinds of
            crazy designs. During this time you should begin planning strategy and deciding how and what
            you want your robot to do.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="approaching_the_game">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Approaching the Game</item>
        <item>Before thinking about how your robot could accomplish the
            game, it is important for you to decide what you want to accomplish! You\'ll need a
            game-plan before you can design a robot. In order to design a robot around the best
            strategy, KING TeC stages a mock game using human players instead of robots immediately
            after Kickoff, revealing any strategies that may otherwise be overlooked.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="game_rules">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Game Rules</item>
        <item>Fully understanding the rules of the new game is critical to the design
            process. Everyone on the team should read the rules at least once and your team should
            appoint a Rules Master, someone who your team can defer to for all rules-related questions.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="getting_materials">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Getting Materials</item>
        <item>While the details of your design may not be set in stone, it is important for your
            team to begin purchasing materials, especially materials that need to be shipped.
            Unfortunately you can\'t build a robot without supplies, and it is much better to be
            waiting for them during Weeks One and Two than during Week Six.
            &lt;br>
            Have your team put together a list of expected materials, and don\'t forget to
            include extras for any parts you think might break.
            Your priority should be getting the parts you need to start building!</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Week Two -->

    <string-array name="prototyping">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Prototyping</item>
        <item>The teams on Einstein Field at the FRC World Championship consistently do one thing right.
            They test and test repeatedly, designing and breaking components of their robot before even
            thinking about assembling them into a finalized design. Prototyping allows teams to find
            flaws in their designs and fix them before it cuts into the crucial later weeks, where time
            and resources need to be spent on programming and drive practice.
            &lt;br>
            KING TeC assembles smaller two/three man teams that work on individual components of the
            robot. How you prototype is up to your team, but it is important to keep the process moving.
            Don\'t let a failure in one part constitute a failure as a whole!</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="chassis_building">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Building the Chassis</item>
        <item>Although you may not have a completely finalized robot design at this point in time, it is
            extremely important that you begin building the chassis. The drive-train is the heart of almost
            every robot design out there, and it is important to get a driving robot as soon as possible. Not
            only will having driving robot guarantee you some level of success on the field, without a
            frame the components and modules you are prototyping will have nowhere to go!</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="drive_practice">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Drive Practice</item>
        <item>When competing at competition, nothing can make or break your teams experience than how
            your drivers work together and with the robot. While six weeks is not a lot of time to build
            a robot, it is important to find time to let your drivers practice. The earlier the better,
            but the season goes fast and we often are only able to practice driving during the last few
            days of the build season.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Week Four -->

    <string-array name="early_programming">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Getting Started Programming</item>
        <item>In order to test your robot, you need to be able to control it. Start with the basics,
            and begin programming one subsystem at a time. It is important to remember that you
            shouldn\'t worry about perfecting the code at this time; save the fine-tuning and control
            loops for later. As long as you can control the subsystems at this point, and are able to
            read from any sensors that you might have, you\'re doing fine.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Week Five -->

    <string-array name="main_programming">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Programming</item>
        <item>By this point, you should be able to control every part of your robot. It is time to
            stop working on implementing new features and perfect the ones you have. This is the time
            to create control loops which make the driver\'s job easier, such as a PID controller.
            Make sure to check if existing functions are available before trying to implement your
            own; they will be easier to use and are much less likely to contain bugs than code you or
            your team writes.
            &lt;br>
            One of the features that is not stressed enough in FRC programming is code reuse.
            When writing the functions for this year\'s robot, think about how you can write the code
            so that it is still viable next year. Although your robot will change from year to year,
            there is no reason you cannot recycle some of the programming ideas and implementations.
            However, you may be required to release the code as open-source if you plan to use code
            from previous years, in order to comply with
            &lt;a href="http://frc-manual.usfirst.org/viewItem/285">R16&lt;/a> of the
            &lt;a href="http://frc-manual.usfirst.org/viewItem/3">Game Manual&lt;/a>.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Week Six -->

    <string-array name="tweaking_programming">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Tweaking Programming</item>
        <item>While you hopefully have the main functionality of your robot programmed by this point,
            odds are you won\'t get everything perfect the first time. Your programmers should be focusing
            on fixing the major bugs and getting everything working, but after that it is time to bring
            in the drive team.
            &lt;br>
            Although programmers like to think they know everything about the robot,
            it is important to remind them that they most likely won\'t be driving it at competition.
            If they will be, your team has lucked out! If not, the programmers should sit down with the
            drive team and fine tune the controls until the drivers are content.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="late_build_changes">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Building the Unexpected</item>
        <item>Like the real world, build season is often full of unexpected surprises. In the case of
            a robot-building emergency, don\'t panic. Last minute changes happen on every team, and the
            important thing to remember is that you can continue building after the six weeks are over.
            &lt;br>
            You are allowed to bring a small amount of robot-related parts to competition, which means
            you can manufacture parts at home and install them on the first day of competition.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="bag_and_tag">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Bagging and Tagging</item>
        <item>While in the past your robot had to be crated up, in recent years a new procedure for sealing
            away your robot has been unveiled. All official events with the exception of the Championship are
            "Bag and Tag" events, meaning that your robot must be suffocated by a giant bag on the last day
            of Build Season. More information is available in the
            &lt;a href="http://frc-manual.usfirst.org/viewItem/8">administrative manual&lt;/a>.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Spirit at the competition -->

    <string-array name="spirit_importance">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Importance of Spirit</item>
        <item>While at competitions it\'s important that you make your team known. The more noticed you
            are by other teams, the more likely you are to get picked for alliance selections. You
            also want to keep the competition energy high because it makes an even more exciting
            atmosphere for everyone in the arena.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="spirit_team_image">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Team Image</item>
        <item>Before competition it is important to develop a team image or look. This look can be
            fun and exciting; teams wear everything from animal costumes to capes and crowns, each
            team coming up with their own look. It can be difficult to make your own image, but just
            keep in mind that it doesn\'t have to be crazy to be recognizable. As winners of the FIRST
            World Championship Imagery Award, KING TeC shows that you don’t have to look over the top
            for your team to stand out.
            &lt;br>
            Start with a team t-shirt. Make your team name and number easily read, this way if another
            team or a judge is looking for your team, you’re easy to find. After developing a shirt, the
            sky is the limit. Teams wear everything from matching shoes, to matching bracelets. Be creative
            and remember to not shy far from your name. If teams will wonder how your mascot is relevant to
            your name, it’s probably not the best idea.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="spirit_swag">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Swag</item>
        <item>Swag is a giveaway item for other teams. Although swag is far from mandatory, it can
            help advertise your team. Many teams do buttons, while at competition you can see people
            completely covered in buttons. Other simple and cost effective ideas are pencils and
            bracelets. Swag gets your team name and number out to other teams. Continue to keep in
            mind your message, your image, and how you want other teams to remember you.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Fundraising -->

    <string-array name="fundraising_obtaining_sponsors">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Obtaining Sponsors</item>
        <item>Sponsorships often give teams large amounts of money for little effort,
            especially when compared to other methods of fundraising. Sponsors can be either
            corporate, at a major business such as JCPenny, or local, with locations that include
            a local hardware store and a restaurant. However, when obtaining sponsors it is
            important to remember that non-monetary sponsorship may be just as valuable as money.
            Many companies can offer mentorship or supply donations.
            &lt;br>The first step to getting sponsors is asking team members if any parents work for
            companies that could potentially offer money, mentors, or donations to the team. This
            option should be explored first because connections make companies much more likely to
            want to support the team. Ask the  parents for the people to contact regarding
            sponsorship at their companies, and call the contacts to schedule meetings with those
            who grant sponsorship. Once a meeting is scheduled, sponsorship is almost guaranteed.
            Prepare an interactive PowerPoint and speech, and be ready to answer questions.
            &lt;br>If no parents work at companies that could sponsor the team or additional
            sponsors are needed, there are many other options. Go to the websites of local teams and
            find out which companies sponsor them, as large companies usually sponsor several teams
            in their base areas. Local companies are also often willing to sponsor robotics teams.
            Although they might not be able to give as much money, having support from the community
            is an important aspect of FIRST.
            &lt;br>More information can be found on the
            &lt;a href="http://www.usfirst.org/roboticsprograms/first-fundraising-toolkit">FIRST Fundraising Toolkit&lt;/a>.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fundraising_grants">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Applying for Grants</item>
        <item>Grants typically offer a one-time source of money for teams. The monetary
            amount, however, is rarely small. FIRST offers grants to its teams, but many of
            these are aimed towards and only eligible to rookie teams. Many corporations
            offer several grants to both rookie and veteran teams. At this time, these companies
            include NASA, Rockwell Automation, and PTC. Local educational foundations and
            donation-based non-profit organizations also often offer grants. When applying for
            grants, a team may apply for a general team grant or for a grant for specific, needed
            items. An example of items to buy with grant money, which may be stated when
            applying for the grant, is the purchase of computers, hard drives, and tablets.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fundraising_major_events">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Major Fundraising Events</item>
        <item>One reliable and consistent way to raise money is to host large fundraising events. These
            events often span several days of work and should be planned well in advance. Although a lot
            of work, these events provide an excellent way to raise funds for your team.
            &lt;br>One example of a major fundraising event is hosting a summer day camp for
            local youth. This doubles as an outreach activity because FIRST supports the introduction
            of STEAM (Science, Technology, Engineering, Art, and Mathematics) in community outreach
            to young people. Teams can charge anywhere from $50 to $250 per student for a one or two
            weeklong day camp. There are many options of concepts to teach the attending students,
            and these include MIT’s Scratch programming and robots built with Vex or FLL kit-of-parts.
            Teams can either host these camps themselves at their high school or at other community
            locations, and local “community education” groups can run and manage the camps.
            &lt;br>Teams can host school-sponsored activities to raise both money and local awareness.
            Planning and holding a themed school dance should raise anywhere from $1,000 to $5,000 per year.
            Examples of themes are winter, Valentine’s Day, and Halloween. Robotic concepts such as
            laser lights and automated decorations can even be incorporated into the dance. Students
            will be drawn to attend the dance with promotions that students DJ the music and there are
            fun, unique elements such as balloon drops.
            &lt;br>Hosting an off-season regional competition spreads awareness of the team and earns
            money. Prices to charge per attending team range from $50 to $500, and this adds up
            quickly if 20+ teams attend. Teams return continually to well-organized events because
            they provide positive networking environments for both the hosts and attendees. If a
            team is small or new to planning an event of such a large magnitude, it can team up with
            one or two other local teams and split the profits.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fundraising_minor_events">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Minor Fundraising Events</item>
        <item>Smaller fundraising events may raise less money, but they are easier to plan and host
            more of. Many successfully spread awareness in a team’s local community. One example is
            bagging groceries at a local supermarket. Past robots can be displayed and, if the store
            allows it, driven. Customers are usually excited to hear about the robots and community
            outreach of a FIRST team, and they are often willing to donate. This typically earns a
            team $500 to $1,500. Another small fundraising event that can be done at a supermarket
            is selling hot dogs outside the building in the summer. Local stores will often donate
            the equipment, and they will possibly donate the supplies. Watch for stores that offer
            this, and request a shift. This can make a team around $500 to $1,000. Many local and
            chain restaurants offer high school teams benefit nights. On these nights, a certain
            percentage of sales is granted to the promoted team. If a team advertises properly, it
            has the potential to earn well over $500 and into the thousands of dollars. When
            combined, these minor fundraising events can earn more money than one or two major
            events.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Pits -->

    <string-array name="pits_design">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Pit Design</item>
        <item>Designing your pit is one of the most important things to do before you head to
            competition. Creating your pit is not something to take lightly considering it
            represents your team in the pits at competitions. There are many different aspects to
            consider when designing your teams pit. One main thing to think about is implementing
            your team\'s name and number into your pit. Your name and number should be clearly visible
            to everyone whether they are judges, other team members/mentors, or volunteers; it is
            very important that your pit is noticeable to all of these people.
            &lt;br>The design of your pit is also supposed to not only display your teams name and
            number but also your teams theme and values. Judges are constantly in the pits so it is
            important that your team’s values are displayed openly. This can be shown by hanging up
            posters, displaying your sponsors names, or even banners. Hanging a banner across the
            top of your pit is an easy way to display a lot of information that can easily be seen
            by everyone. As you can see, there are many ways to show your teams theme and values in
            your pit design. The best advice we can give is to have fun and be creative!</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pits_organization">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Organization</item>
        <item>Organization is one of the most important things in your team’s pit. Without a system
            of organization it is almost inevitable that you will lose something. There are many
            different ways to organize your pit. You will have a ton of tools and items you will be
            bringing with you that will all seem to end up in your pit. It is a good idea to have
            boxes, cabinets, etc. so items are not lost or stolen. Organizing your pit crew\'s tools
            is a vitally important thing for your team’s success because if your robot breaks during
            competition you want to be able to find these tools easily. It is also important to leave
            tools that are commonly needed during competition in a close by place so they can be accessed easily.
            &lt;br>Aside from the tools there are many other things that will need to be organized
            in your pit whether they are computers, batteries, or even jackets. It is a good idea
            to have an easily accessible area with the batteries so you can quickly change them when
            necessary. Computers are not something you likely want to leave out in the open, even if
            there is someone always in your pit, it is best to put them in a safe place such as a
            cabinet or even just under a table out of site. Jackets and other such items can easily
            be put into a box or crate so they are not taking up space inside the pit. Lastly, always
            remember to leave space to work when needed.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pits_crew">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Pit Crew</item>
        <item>The pit crew are some of the most crucial people off the field. It is important to
            allow them the space necessary in the pit for immediate work and for those moments of
            rushed panic. The pit crew should be ready for anything at any time. The crew should be
            about 5-6 people so there is not too few or too many people in the pits. The pits can
            easily get crowded so it is important to not have too many people around so there is
            plenty of space to work on the robot. With the drive team and the pit crew constantly
            in and out of the pits it’s important to keep a minimal amount of people besides them in
            the area to avoid overcrowding. A last reminder, it is very important to have mechanical
            people in the pit crew, but a programmer is just as necessary for a successful robot.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pits_judges">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Talking With Judges</item>
        <item>Talking with judges is obviously one of the most important parts of the pits. Judges
            are constantly walking through the pits at competitions so don’t forget to always show
            gracious professionalism. When judges come and talk to teams in the pits they are truly
            curious and eager to learn about your team and your robot. The judges will ask questions
            that are either relevant to your robot or your team so it is wise to have experts of both
            in your pits. When talking to judges always be informative. It is also important that
            when judges come to your team’s pit that a team member is doing most or all of the
            talking, not a mentor or parent. The judges are there to talk to the team, not the
            mentors.
            &lt;br>While the majority of the questions asked in the pit will be about your team\'s
            robot the judges will also be looking for contenders for the other awards at the
            competition. This will be even amplified if you are competing for the Chairman\'s award.
            It is important to have an expert on your team’s outreach, marketing, and fundraising
            side of your team in the pits as well. They will help answer these questions for the
            judges. Judges are also not the only ones coming to talk in the pits; you will have pit
            scouters, alliance partners, and volunteers always coming by also. Remember to always
            be in a good mood!</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Chairman's -->

    <string-array name="chairmans_about">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>What is Chairman\'s?</item>
        <item>As stated in the FRC Manual section 6.4.1: \"The Chairman\'s Award was created to keep
            the central focus of FRC on the ultimate goal of transforming the culture in ways that
            will inspire greater levels of respect and honor for science and technology, as well as
            encouraging more of today\'s youth to become scientists, engineers, and technologists.
            &lt;br>The Chairman\'s Award represents the spirit of FIRST. It honors the team that, in
            the judges\' estimation, best represents a model for other teams to emulate, and which
            embodies the goals and purpose of FIRST. It remains FIRST\'s most prestigious award.\"
            &lt;br>Any non-rookie team can compete for the Chairman\'s Award. It focuses on a team\'s
            current and previous year. The Chairman\'s Award is one of three ways to qualify for the
            FIRST Championship. The winners are given the opportunity to compete at the FIRST
            Championship to be inducted into the First Hall of Fame. The FIRST Hall of Fame consists
            of teams that have won the Chairman’s Award at the FIRST Championship. A new rule for the
            2014 season states that a team can compete for the Chairman\'s Award at every regional they
            attend until they win. In previous seasons, teams could only compete at one regional event.
            &lt;br>Chairman\'s is composed largely of three different pieces: the written portion,
            the speech, and the video.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="chairmans_writing">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>The Written Portion</item>
        <item>The written piece of Chairman’s has two main parts, the essay and the executive
            summary. The essay is a 10,000 character written explanation of how your team spreads
            the mission of FIRST. At first 10,000 characters can seem like a lot, but you will most
            likely have to shrink your essay in order to meet these requirements. While writing your
            essay do not worry about word count. You will be better off writing your essay and them
            combining and removing sentences. It\'s important that you start your essay early that way
            your speech and video can play off of it.
            &lt;br>The executive summary is a series of question that you will have to answer. The
            majority of the questions have a 500 character word limit. You will also include your
            team name, number and sponsors. These short answers have to do with how your team has
            spread FIRST, and how FIRST has impacted your team. Along with the written pieces, you
            will need to submit four photos at the same time. These photos are to show judges how
            you’ve spread FIRST. These four photos can be no more than 1.0 MB of memory.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="chairmans_speech">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>The Speech</item>
        <item>Although teams can probably talk about how they spread the mission of FIRST for hours,
            teams are only given a short five minute time period to tell judges all about how they
            impact their community. After the five minute presentation time, teams will have a five
            minute question answer session. Teams must send in up to three representatives - members
            or mentors.
            &lt;br>&lt;br>The Chairman\'s presentation can seem very scary but here are some tips to
            keep in mind while creating and performing your presentation:
            &lt;br>&lt;br>&#8226;\tDon\'t let the judges emotions get to you. They have had long days of
            speeches and are probably very tired and bored. Don\'t let this get to you while presenting.
            &lt;br>&lt;br>&#8226;\tThe room may be very small; you should bring only what is necessary.
            &lt;br>&lt;br>&#8226;\tExactly how much time you have depends on the judges. Some judges may start
            the clock when you start the drawer.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="chairmans_video">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>The Video</item>
        <item>The Chairman\'s video can be no longer than three minutes nor shorter than one. The
            Chairman\'s video is mandatory in order to compete for the award. Before judges make
            their final decision as to who wins between a few final teams, they watch these videos.
            The video is very important because it is the last thing the judges will remember. When
            a team wins, the video is broadcasted to the rest of the teams on the big screen at regional
            or district events.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Tournaments -->

    <string-array name="tournaments_about">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Why Off-Season Tournament\'s</item>
        <item>The main reason for off season regionals are to train rookie team members and get back
            into the swing of robotics. Before the real regionals begin, it is very useful to give
            the new team members a taste of what to expect. These mini competitions also give teams
            a great opportunity to train members whether it is in driving, scouting or spirit.
            These competitions are hosted by FRC teams and are one day events normally held in
            gymnasiums of the hosting team. Around thirty teams can be found at these regionals.
            Official FIRST fields are shipped to the location and official FIRST judges, refs, and
            tech managers are running the event. These regionals provide a nice opportunity for
            FIRST volunteers to get trained into leadership positions. Awards are given out and
            winners are crowned all in good fun.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Outreach -->

    <string-array name="outreach_about">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Outreach</item>
        <item>Teams spread the mission of FIRST in many different ways. Outreach events are important
            to help get your team name out into the world of FIRST and out into your community. Your
            team can do many forms of outreach in order to spread the world of science and technology.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="outreach_mentoring">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Mentoring</item>
        <item>One way to spread STEM is through mentoring other teams. You might consider starting a
            FTC team to form a funnel program at your school into your FRC team. You can also start
            other teams in your surrounding area through presenting at their schools. Whether its FLL,
            FTC or FRC, kids are given the opportunity to learn about science and technology and FIRST
            is an exciting organization to have fun in.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="outreach_demonstrations">
        <item>fragment_pager_item</item>
        <item>Demonstrations</item>
        <item>Whether it is at your local grocery store or at a science museum, demonstrations are a
            great way to reach out to your local community. You can allow kids to drive the robots
            and teach adults about its benefits. Demonstrations are a great opportunity for your team
            to find interested people and get them involved. A few fun places to give demonstrations
            is at local schools, malls, and museums.</item>
        <item>ic_kt</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
</resources>